let savollar5 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "aware",
        answer: "C. xabardor",
        options: [
            "A. ko'rgan",
            "B. eshitgan",
            "C. xabardor",
            "D. unutilgan"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "badly",
        answer: "B. yomon",
        options: [
            "A. qo'shiq",
            "B. yomon",
            "C. o'rtacha",
            "D. tez"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "to belong",
        answer: "A. tegishli bo'lmoq",
        options: [
            "A. tegishli bo'lmoq",
            "B. yo'qotmoq",
            "C. topmoq",
            "D. qo'ymoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "to continue",
        answer: "D. davom etmoq",
        options: [
            "A. to'xtatmoq",
            "B. boshlamoq",
            "C. tugatmoq",
            "D. davom etmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "error",
        answer: "B. xato",
        options: [
            "A. omadsizlik",
            "B. xato",
            "C. muvaffaqiyatsizlik",
            "D. yiqilish"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "experience",
        answer: "C. taasurot",
        options: [
            "A. bilim",
            "B. o'rganish",
            "C. taasurot",
            "D. dars"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "field",
        answer: "A. keng maydon",
        options: [
            "A. keng maydon",
            "B. daryo",
            "C. o'rmon",
            "D. tog'"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "to hurt",
        answer: "D. jarohatlamoq",
        options: [
            "A. davolamoq",
            "B. qutqarmoq",
            "C. yiqilmoq",
            "D. jarohatlamoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "judgment",
        answer: "B. fikr",
        options: [
            "A. suhbat",
            "B. fikr",
            "C. savol",
            "D. javob"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "likely",
        answer: "C. ehtimol",
        options: [
            "A. aniq",
            "B. hech qachon",
            "C. ehtimol",
            "D. shubhali"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "normal",
        answer: "A. normal",
        options: [
            "A. normal",
            "B. o'ziga xos",
            "C. g'ayrioddiy",
            "D. qiziqarli"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "rare",
        answer: "D. noyob",
        options: [
            "A. keng tarqalgan",
            "B. ko'p",
            "C. odatiy",
            "D. noyob"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "to relax",
        answer: "C. dam olmoq",
        options: [
            "A. o'ynamoq",
            "B. maza qilmoq",
            "C. dam olmoq",
            "D. yotmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "to request",
        answer: "B. so'ramoq",
        options: [
            "A. buyurmoq",
            "B. so'ramoq",
            "C. to'xtatmoq",
            "D. olmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "to reside",
        answer: "A. istiqomat qilmoq",
        options: [
            "A. istiqomat qilmoq",
            "B. sayohat qilmoq",
            "C. o'qimoq",
            "D. ishlamoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "result",
        answer: "C. natija",
        options: [
            "A. savol",
            "B. qaror",
            "C. natija",
            "D. maqsad"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "to roll",
        answer: "B. yumalatmoq",
        options: [
            "A. aylantirmoq",
            "B. yumalatmoq",
            "C. itarmoq",
            "D. ko'chirmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "since",
        answer: "D. dan beri",
        options: [
            "A. keyin",
            "B. ilgari",
            "C. hozir",
            "D. dan beri"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "visible",
        answer: "A. ko'rinadigan",
        options: [
            "A. ko'rinadigan",
            "B. ochiq",
            "C. tiniq",
            "D. katta"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "wild",
        answer: "C. yovvoyi",
        options: [
            "A. badjaxl",
            "B. yirtqich",
            "C. yovvoyi",
            "D. qo'rqinchli"
        ]
    }
];
